forwardon.com 2012-03-23

# forwardOn: Privacy Policy

**About forwardOn**

forwardOn is a content sharing website which makes it safer, rewarding and more fun for everyone to share fun email forwards. Plus, on forwardOn, users can view fun content that people around the world are sharing with their friends. 

Please read the following to learn about our privacy policy. By visiting forwardOn website or using any forwardOn services, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

**Privacy**

Users' privacy is extremely important to us and we are committed to safeguarding the information you entrust to us. forwardOn will not disclose information about our users without express permission unless the release of said information is required by government subpoena. 

**Information Collection**

forwardOn may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online registration, forms and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. We may also collect information about how Users interact with our website . This information is obtained through analysis of server logs and through the use of "cookies" placed on user machines. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on a PC to identify the User should they visit the website again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our website. 

In addition, any personal information, pictures or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (post via email or list on the website) will become publicly available and can be collected and used by others. 

**Information Usage**

forwardOn may use personally identifiable information collected through our website to contact Users regarding products and services offered by forwardOn and its trusted affiliates. We may also use information collected through our website for research regarding the effectiveness of the website and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of forwardOn, and its trusted affiliates. 

forwardOn may use your email to send information about related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions from forwardOn or it’s affiliates. You may also receive notification e-mails from forwardOn, which inform you of actions (e.g. invites from friends) that have been performed on the site. 

**Information Disclosure**

forwardOn will not disclose information about our users without express permission unless the release of said information is required by a trusted affiliate to facilitate action requested by the client, or is required by government subpoena. 

**Third-party advertisers**

forwardOn allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on forwardOn.com. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on forwardOn. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

**Children Under 18 Years of Age**

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the forwardOn website. As a result, forwardOn does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that forwardOn has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents' permission before using forwardOn or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

forwardOn reserves the right to change this privacy policy, and/or any part thereof, at any time. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you via email or by posting an announcement on the Website. You understand that the most recent version of this Agreement will be located on the forwardOn Web site under Privacy Policy. 

**Conditions of Use**

If you decide to visit forwardOn website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. 

**Questions**

Please contact us with any questions regarding our privacy policy by emailing us at [admin@forwardon.com](mailto:admin@forwardon.com?subject=Privacy%20question).
